4.
Thank you.
Here
we go.
3.
Good,
man.
All right.
All right. So, uh, first off, uh,
jacked about tonight and, uh, being able
to get Lee Hunter and Chris Brazzle. Um,
two guys that we obviously thought very
high of. Uh, start off with Lee just
like big physical point of attack guy
who's athletic enough to get up and down
the line of scrimmage. Uh, makes a lot
of plays. Uh, eats up a lot of blockers
for the linebackers. is a guy we're
really excited about. Uh Chris Brazzle,
obviously a big long linear receiver
with a big catch radius. Uh can adjust
really well downfield. Uh he's got the
speed to take the top off, take it the
distance. Um so another guy again we're
extremely excited about. Um good day. Um
work's far from over. Um, but yeah,
we're we're headed in the right
direction. We feel good about the draft
so far and you know, we're going to keep
building and adding pieces and and
following the board and um, you know,
because that's what we've really been
doing up to this point is just kind of
following the board and uh, letting that
kind of guide us.
>> Why' you get straight up?
>> You want to say anything? Sorry.
>> Oh, just yeah, I'm just excited about
the guys and and again just committed to
the process of taking the best player on
the board and um you know we couldn't
pass up an opportunity for a violent
player like Lee and then uh Chris, you
know, he's one of my favorite players in
the draft. um just his film over the
last two years, you know, um when you
look at two lane and then you look at
Tennessee and you kind of combine all of
it, you're going to get a full picture
of a route tree, uh body control,
ability to do those things. And of
course, just the ability to stretch the
field and um and really put stress on
teams uh from a vertical standpoint. And
so, you know, we weren't expecting Chris
to be there. You know, we were sitting
there waiting and he's he just kept, you
know, dropping right to us. And um just
what a great opportunity for us to just
again just add to that room just another
element, another dimension and uh and
create a competitive roster.
>> Let's go ahead, Mike.
>> Sure. Uh what made you guys trade up a
couple of picks to to get Lee?
>> Um the board was kind of thinning out at
the time. Um, we just felt like, hey,
like this is like the last guy that we
kind of had a little at in the higher
rounds and we just felt like, hey, let's
let's go get our guy instead of kind of
settling for somebody else. We're like,
let's go get our guy. Uh, we were all
convicted on him. Uh, not only as a
player, but as a person. Do you see him
as being a nose that can kind of
complement a rotation of Turk and Bobby
or how how do you how do you guys view
him from a from a style standpoint?
>> Yeah, let's get him in here and see what
he can do. You know, um just in our
schemes and and uh that part will make a
lot of sense for us. But when you're an
interior defensive lineman, it all
starts with violence and uh that's one
thing that he kind of characterized
himself. You know, what's your play
style? Violence, you know, and
repeatedly said violence. you know, just
um you know, just the way that he's
disruptive and um and explosive at the
line of scrimmage and then we'll figure
out the pieces from there. But we have a
really good group in there, versatile
guys that uh we can use in different
ways.
>> And I would add too like the way that we
play our D line, like
>> there's really not like starters like
you know, we're rotating a bunch so he's
just going to be in that rotation. He
can play nose, he can play a little DN
in the 34. Um so he brings a lot of
versatility. Were you concerned that the
Jets might take him 50?
>> I was a little concerned that, you know,
Dline's pretty thin this draft. Um, so I
I felt like, hey, let's let's go get our
guy. Let's make sure we get who we want
and that's why we traded up and got
aggressive.
>> The first two picks obviously on the
line, what does that say about, you
know, was that something you really
wanted to address coming in? Yeah, I
think uh you know, coach and I and and
the rest of the staff like we believe in
building building it up front and and
winning the line of scrimmage and and I
think if you can win the line of
scrimmage on both sides of the ball, you
have a chance to win every single game.
So, yeah, that's definitely a point of
emphasis.
Dave, uh, you haven't had a guy with
this type of speed in this offense, uh,
so far, a guy that can, you know, get
downfield, like you said, vertically
consistently. What is it about a guy
that has that type of size and speed
that makes him so dynamic outside of the
router that you
>> Well, it's the ability to uh take those
traits, but then also to play the ball
in the air. Um, one of the things that
Chris showed is his ability to play the
deep ball, land on his feet, finish the
play. Um, that's something that's very
rare where a lot of times you'll see a
guy high point a ball, lay out for it,
they end up on the ground. Um, he's just
got a special balance with how he
finishes which translates that speed and
that size, you know. Um, so just all
those things, you know, and and and
we've seen how we've been able to use
Xavier, T-Mac, Jaylen, you know, with
all the uh intermediate stuff and have
gone down the field a little bit, you
know, and taken some opportunities, but,
you know, I think about the space
created when they know this is a real
burner um and what that does to
safeties, what that does to corners and
just creating space um for the whole
group.
>> You mentioned a few guys in that wide
receiver room. Can you have too much
talent in in a room?
>> Absolutely not. You you just, you know,
you continue to add great players and
and it elevates everybody's play. Um how
that plays out, we'll see. You know,
there's a lot of work that's got to be
done from now until we start the season.
And um it's just great to continue to
add those guys so that we have different
elements and and increase the level of
competition in the room.
to call Chris one of your favorite
players in the draft. Was there a
particular game, particular play that
kind of pops in your mind that you kind
of point to and say that's who this guy
is?
>> Um, I can't say anything specifically,
but just the body of work, his ability
to have the vertical speed and threat,
but then his his ability to drop his
weight, get in and out of breaks really
efficiently is one of the things that I
was so impressed with. And um, you know,
in our conversations, you know, as we
were going through the process, I was
like, "Guys, look at this." Typically,
when a guyy's 6'4, they don't have that
type of bend and flexibility and power
to stop on a dime and get out. That's
really valuable when you're a vertical
threat. Um because it's a two-way go for
you at that point. And then of course it
was just the uh the acrobatic body
balance and ability to stay on his feet
to track the ball down the field um that
I really just uh fell in love with, you
know, and uh and looked, you know, was
really excited to get an opportunity to
work with those skills.
>> You guys had him in on a 30, I think.
>> Yeah, we did. What was that visit like
with him?
>> It was great. It was great. Uh, you
know, great personality. Uh, obviously
another guy that loves football and, you
know, he bleeds it. And I think on our
call when we called him, you could hear
the excitement in his voice about coming
here and competing and adding to that
wide receiver room.
>> Any texts from Bryce tonight about
Brazil?
>> I haven't looked at my phone yet. I
haven't looked at my phone yet, but I'm
sure I'm sure Bryce will be happy about
that.
>> Dave, your um your response or
assessment of the inerson visit with
Chris?
>> Yeah, so we had him at the combine
first. Um and and then we brought him in
for the 30 visit, get to spend a little
bit more time. And what impressed me
about him is just when he talks about
what he was working on, that's something
that's really big for me, having
receiver coaching background. um when I
can hear a guy talk about the the
different skills that they're working
on, the drills they're doing. Um he's
got a he's got a brother, you know, and
like they're doing one-on- ones and
they're he he loves the game. He's a um
he's about his craft and you can see
that on the field. You can see how um
how compact and and efficient he is with
his footwork and different things. But
that always impresses me when a guy has
a plan for what they're trying to
improve upon. Dan, there are so many
kind of players that fit what you guys
want to do that got a lot of hype
entering the draft. Is there originally
it felt like you were going to come in
after the end of the third round? Why
did you guys kind of stop and come up
now as opposed to maybe tracking the
rest of the draft possibilities end
today?
>> Why did we come up in the
>> like the draft is still going on?
>> Oh, got you. Yeah. I mean, there's still
guys out there, but, you know, we traded
up once and obviously we had to give one
of our fives and um we got a six back,
but you know, I think um in our
situation like we feel good about where
we're at and what our board looks like
and and we'll be ready for tomorrow.
>> Think you're averaging like 6'2, 63 in
this receiver room now. What kind of how
important was it to establish that
identity and what does it do for your
offense to have a receiver like that?
>> Just great players. Uh we're not really
necessarily trying to set a prototype.
We just happen to continue have
opportunities to bring in these massive
men, you know, and um all the way down
to Bryson Tumine who's 6'5 and goes
about 220. You know, they're they're uh
these guys are rugged in the run game.
That's really important to us. That's
something that that Brad uh harps on
that Rob Moore is really serious about.
Um because we know we're going to run
the ball and um and that length and size
does help us with some of the different
things uh that we do with the run game.
And then of course just like uh creating
an advantage, you know, um as a target
when you when you have that type of size
and length, you know, length is very
forgiving in terms of getting body
position and finishing on the ball. And
that's what we've seen out of our guys.
Um being able to make those plays in
contested situations and and now we got
a guy who's who's tall and he's also
really fast, you know, and so uh his
length and all those things will
continue to help him in the speed. Also
>> along those lines, there was a lot of
speculation that you guys wanted like a
yards after catch guy, somebody you
could also involve in the run game from
a receiver standpoint. Was that a thing
and it just didn't quite fit with with
your board?
>> Um, I think he does have a little run
after catch. Um, you know, obviously
he's got the 437 speed. Um, so he is a
guy that can, you know, if he gets it
and he hits a crease, he has the speed
to take it the distance. And, um, you
know, where we're at making the playoffs
and kind of being a little further back
in the order, obviously that's going to
limit you and, you know, who's going to
be available to you as well. So, um,
we're just jacked that we could get
Chris there at the end. Maybe not a
position of need, but is there a certain
position in this draft that's kind of
gone differently than maybe you had
projected or or maybe a trend that
you've noticed in these first three?
>> Yeah, I mean, I think you just see, you
know, once uh like the tight ends, like
the tight ends went on a run there for a
little bit. The wide outs started kind
of going on a run there towards the end
when we picked Chris. Um, so yeah, I
mean I think you know once one guys
starts getting picked and I think teams
start seeing guys fall off the board
kind of makes everybody a little antsy
and you know they start picking that
position. So um I don't know if there's
one particular position but I think you
know once you see you know a particular
guy come off the board I think teams get
a little spooked and um and they'll go
on runs. Dan, as you look at the as you
look at the roster as a whole and as
it's got better and deeper, does it
change the way you look at day three of
the draft just in terms of how guys fit,
whether they make the roster, that kind
of thing?
>> Yeah, I think uh the big thing is going
to be how can guys contribute on special
teams. Um, you know, we we only have a
certain amount of guys we can dress on
game day. So, you know, these guys, you
know, here towards the end of the draft,
they're going to have to be good
teamers, you know, to be able to make
our team and and contribute the way we
want them to.
>> Does that look like linebackers and
safeties, tight ends?
>> I mean, yeah, it could be it could be a
combination of of guys. That's a good
try though.
>> No, team.
>> Yeah, definitely. Yeah, it's um yeah,
usually linebackers, tight ends, it can
be corners, safeties, you know,
returners, you know, so we'll explore
every option and, you know, we'll pick
the right guy for us.
>> Does Chris have any He doesn't have any
return background, does he?
>> No, he's No.
>> Yeah.
>> All right, everybody. Good. Thank you.
>> Thank you. Appreciate it.
>> Thank you.